So I think data can actually make us more human.
Я думаю, что информация может сделать нас более человечными.
We're collecting and creating all kinds of data about how we're living our lives,
Мы собираем и создаем все типы информации про то, как мы живем,
and it's enabling us to tell some amazing stories.
и это даёт нам возможность рассказывать поразительные истории.
Recently, a wise media theorist Tweeted,
Недавно, один мудрый медиа теоретик написал в Twitter:
"The 19th century culture was defined by the novel,
«Культура 19-ого века определялась романом,
the 20th century culture was defined by the cinema,
культура 20-ого века определялась кино,
and the culture of the 21st century
а культура 21-ого
will be defined by the interface."
будет определяться интерфейсом».
And I believe this is going to prove true.
И я уверен, что это подтвердится.
Our lives are being driven by data,
Нашими жизнями управляет информация,
and the presentation of that data is an opportunity
и способ её подачи – это возможность
for us to make some amazing interfaces that tell great stories.
для нас создать необычные интерфейсы, которые рассказывают удивительные истории
So I'm going to show you a few of the projects
Я покажу вам несколько проектов,
that I've been working on over the last couple years
над которыми я работал последние два года.